https://horseshoeresort.com/privacy-policy-horseshoe/

ActivitiesActivities – HomeCOVID-19 Policies & ProceduresWinter ActivitiesSummer & Fall ActivitiesLake HorseshoeCamp HorseshoeEventsMembershipsSkiSki – HomeAlpine Season PassesAlpine Lift Tickets and RentalsCross Country SkiingSnow SchoolSchool Group ProgramsTuning ServicesTrail MapRecent Resort InvestmentsSafety and Risk AwarenessGolfGolf – HomeGolf MembershipRates & Tee Times2020 Golf Protocol9 Hole Valley ScorecardGolf Ontario Handicap TableBikeBike – HomeDownhill Mountain Bike LessonsTrail MapsBike ServiceBiking Ride Guides2020 Downhill Mountain Biking ProtocolStayStay – HomeThe Inn At HorseshoeCopeland HouseSlopeside CondosEatEat – HomeEleven01 Taphouse + KitchenCrazy Horse Sports Bar & GrillShoe BrewAlpine CafeteriaPreferred MembershipGroupsGroup – HomeMeetingsRecreation GroupsWeddingsCelebrationsCOVID-19 Policies & ProceduresSpaSpa – HomeSpa ServicesSpa Specials2020 Spa ProtocolReal Estate Book Online:
Check-in:
Check-out:
Adults: 12345678910111213141516171819
Children: 0123456
Promo Code:
Ages:   Child 1: 012345678910111213141516
Child 2: 012345678910111213141516
Child 3: 012345678910111213141516
Child 4: 012345678910111213141516
Child 5: 012345678910111213141516
Child 6: 012345678910111213141516
Home > Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to Horseshoe Resort. To help protect your privacy, we adhere to the following guidelines:This web site will explicitly ask when it needs information that personally identifies our customers or allows it to contact our customers (“Personal Information”). When possible, this web site will provide our customers with the means to make sure that Personal Information is correct and currentThis web site and its service providers use Personal Information to operate the sites, provide services, and to inform our customers of new features, services, and products. This web site may also carefully select other companies to send our customers information about their products or services.* If this web site intends to use Personal Information for a Secondary Use, we will not do so until we have provided our customers with an opportunity to affirmatively select such service.This web site may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with applicable law or with legal process served on the Horseshoe Resort site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Horseshoe Resort or this site, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Horseshoe Resort, the site, or the public. If at any time a customer believes that this web site has not adhered to these principles, please notify Horseshoe Resort by e-mail at info@horseshoeresort.com  and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.Our customers should also be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of our internet servers and through the use of “cookies”. “Cookies” are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a system and damage files.Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to each customer that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows a customer to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide customers with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on this web site.
